beangroup.com 2019-12-25

# Bean Group

We at Bean Group (referred to as "We," "Us," or "Our") recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of certain information collected about the users and visitors of Our Web Site (referred to as "User," "You" or "Your"). This Privacy Policy discloses what information We gather, how We use it, and how to correct or change it. At Bean Group, it is Our intention to give You an understanding about how We collect Your information and the use We make of it in the course of Our business.

To that end, Bean Group gathers two types of information about You: 1) data that Users provide through optional, voluntary registration on Our Web Site, and 2) data that Bean Group gathers through aggregated tracking, mainly by tallying Web pages that are viewed by Users throughout Our Web Site.

However, be assured that Bean Group will not disclose Personal Information (as defined herein) to third parties without Your consent, except as may be noted in this Privacy Policy or disclosed to You when the information is submitted.

**How Does Bean Group Collect Information?**

**Optional Registration**  
We collect information by specifically requesting it from You. Generally this occurs when You register at the Web Site or request information or a service. Usually, We and Our business partners use Your information to operate the Web Site and to deliver services. Bean Group also uses Your information to inform You about other products and/or services available from Bean Group and Bean Group-affiliates.

**Use of Tracking**  
Use of Internet Protocol ("IP") Addresses: An IP address is a unique number that is automatically assigned to Your computer whenever You are surfing the Internet so that Your computer can be identified by the main computers, known as "Web servers," that "serve up" Web pages. This allows Us to identify and gather general information and data about You, such as the Web pages You view.

Bean Group collects IP addresses for the purposes of: helping Us diagnose problems with Our main computers, for system administration, to report aggregated information to Our business partners, and to audit the use of Our Web Site. When Users request Web pages from Our Web Site, Our Web servers log the User's IP address. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a User's session will be logged, but the User will remain anonymous to Us. For example, We collect and/or track the home server domain name, the type of computer, and the type of Web browser used by You to access this Web Site. Such collection and tracking information is gathered by Us as You navigate through this Web Site, and shall be used by Us for Our business purposes only.

We can, and will, use IP addresses to identify You when We feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with Our Web Site Terms of Use or to protect Our service, site, Users, or others.

**Use Of Cookies**  
What are cookies? Cookies are small pieces of information that a Web site sends to Your computer for record-keeping purposes, which information is stored in a file on Your computer's hard drive. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for You by saving Your preferences so that We can use the saved information to facilitate Your use of Our Web Site when You return to the Web Site. Cookies do not tell Us Your individual identity unless You have chosen to provide it to Us. We never save credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and as such, You will find that most major Web sites use them.

By showing how and when Users use the Web Site, cookies help Us see which areas of the Web Site are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Web Site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies.

Most cookies expire after a defined period of time, or You can delete Your cookie file at any time. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset Your Web browser to refuse cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of Bean Group and/or Bean Group-affiliates' services will not function properly or may be considerably slower if You refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, You will not be able to set personalized preferences, and/or may have difficulty completing marketing transactions.

Bean Group and/or Bean Group-affiliates have two (2) primary uses for cookies. First, We use them to specify a User's preferences. Second, We use cookies to track Web site usage trends and patterns. This helps Us understand Our Users' needs better and improve areas of Our Web Site. While both of these activities depend on the use of cookies, You have the option of disabling (refusing) the cookies via Your Web browser preferences.

You may occasionally get cookies from Our business partners. Bean Group and/or Bean Group-affiliates do not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by such third-party Web servers is standard in the Internet industry.

**With Whom Does Bean Group Share Information?**  
As a general rule, Bean Group will not disclose any specific personal information that You submit to Us about You ("Personal Information") in a manner that connects You with the Personal Information, except when We have Your permission or under special circumstances, such as when We believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the ways that Your Personal Information may be disclosed.

**Business Partners & Sponsors:**  
Bean Group may disclose some or all of Your Personal Information to business partners or sponsors, but this use will be specifically described to You prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. Many promotions offer opportunities to request additional information from sponsors. By requesting more information, You give Bean Group permission to transfer Your Personal Information to the sponsor so they can fulfill Your request. In many instances, only Your e-mail address will be shared. If more Personal Information will be shared with the sponsor, You will be notified prior to the transfer.

**Third Party & Aggregate Data:**  
From time to time, You may be offered the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from third parties. If You opt to receive information from these third parties, Bean Group will (with Your permission) share Your name and e-mail address with such third parties. Under confidentiality agreements, Bean Group may match Personal Information with third party data. Also, Bean Group may keep track of what portions of the Web Site Users are visiting and other User statistics, and aggregate this information to help Us create a better experience for Users of Our Web Site. This is all done without knowing Your name or other Personal Information in order to describe Our viewers and services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

**Other:**  
Bean Group may also disclose account information in special cases when We have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Our Terms of Use, or may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with any of Bean Group's rights or property, other Users, or anyone else. Bean Group may disclose or access account information when We believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that We deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve Our products and services.

**How Can You Control the Usage Of Information?**  
In case You change Your mind or some personal information changes (such as Your zip code or e-mail address), We will try to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal information that You give us. We also give You the opportunity to control the communications We direct to You. If a User wishes to update personal information or objects to any usage provided herein for any reason, he/she may contact: [privacy@beangroup.com?](mailto:privacy@beangroup.com "Email to privacy@beangroup.com")

**What Happens When You Link to a Third Party Site?**  
You should be aware that when You are on Bean Group's and/or Bean Group-affiliates' Web Site You can hyperlink, or be directed to, other Web sites that are beyond Our control and/or outside Our service. For example, if You "click" on a banner advertisement or a Bean Group search result, the "click" may transfer You off Our Web Site. These other Web sites may include sites of advertisers, sponsors, and partners that may use Our and/or Bean Group-affiliates' logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other Web sites may send their own cookies to Users, collect data, or solicit Information.

Bean Group and Bean Group-affiliates do not control such Web sites, and, therefore, are not responsible for their contents or the hyperlinks or advertising they choose to place on such Web sites. Bean Group's and/or Bean Group-affiliates' inclusion of hyperlinks to these Web sites do not imply any endorsement of the material on such Web sites or any association with their operators. Our Privacy Policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, which is beyond Bean Group's and/or Bean Group-affiliates' control.

Please keep in mind that whenever You give out information on-line (for example, via message boards or forums) that information can be collected and used by people You do not know. While Bean Group and Bean Group-affiliates strive to protect Users' information and privacy, We cannot guarantee the security of any information You disclose on-line, and You disclose such information at Your own risk.

**Is Information Secure from Others Using the Bean Group Web Site?**  
The security of all information associated with Our Users is an important concern to Us. We exercise care in providing secure transmission of Your information from Your computer to Our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while We strive to protect Your information, Bean Group and Bean Group-affiliates can't ensure or warrant the security of any information You transmit to Us or from Our on-line products or services, and You do so at Your own risk. Once We receive Your transmission, The Michael Bean Group uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of Your information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers (SSL). However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

By using Our Web Site, You signify Your agreement to Bean Group's Privacy Policy. **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEB SITE.** Your continued use of Bean Group's and/or Bean Group-affiliates' Web sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean You accept those changes.
